time flies
时间过得很快
Do you like this place?
你喜欢这个地方吗？
Yes
是的
again
再次
next time
下次
Let's meet our friends
让我们和朋友们见面吧
OK
好的
we have been together for a long time
我们已经在一起很久了
we have never met your friends before
我们以前从未见过你的朋友
We'll see you when we get back
我们回来时会见到你
do not be afraid
不要害怕
What did you eat?
你吃了什么？
chocolate
巧克力
let's go
我们走吧
Many auction participants
众多拍卖参与者
They have submitted the auction documents
他们已提交拍卖文件
Chinese content
中国内容
different
不同的
we got
我们得到了
Mr. Zhang didn’t understand
张先生没听懂
Real card
真卡
we counted
我们数过
Mr. Zhang’s situation
张先生的情况
in danger
在危险之中
Yaoyao is not sure yet?
瑶瑶还没确定吗？
she said she needed some time
她说她需要一些时间
we don't have time
我们没有时间
Let’s start Plan B right away
我们马上开始Plan B
Go to Tianhai
前往天海
Instantly
立即地
OK
好的
they are back
他们回来了
On Tianhai Expressway
天海高速上
10 kilometers left
还剩10公里
ten kilometers
十公里
OK
好的
We set up a switch in the cost terminal
我们在成本终端设置了一个开关
As soon as someone appears
人一出现
We will arrest him immediately
我们将立即逮捕他
OK
好的
It's beautiful outside
外面很漂亮
your man
你的男人
he is no longer trustworthy
他不再值得信任
I still have a chance for revenge
我还有报仇的机会
i think you have the ability
我认为你有能力
But you should give up cutting off your arms
但你应该放弃砍掉你的手臂
This way you can continue your mission
这样您就可以继续执行任务
I will deal with him
我会对付他
he is your partner
他是你的伙伴
He knows the organization
他了解这个组织
Located in Tianhai
位于天海
If it falls into the hands of Guoan
如果落到国安手里
Not very good
不是很好
To serve you and order
为您服务并订购
Understood
明白了
Don't worry
不用担心
Your new partner is much better than him
你的新搭档比他好得多
Have you started plan B?
你开始B计划了吗？
Yes
是的
Now Guoan
现在国安
it is close to the foundation of the organization
它接近组织的基础
if we don't
如果我们不这样做
I'm afraid it's too late
恐怕为时已晚
I sent Tony to deal with her.
我派托尼去对付她
Priority now
现在优先
you have to take off your tail
你必须把你的尾巴去掉
be safe
注意安全
Understood
明白了
I've prepared something for you
我已经为你准备好了东西
It seems like this period
好像这个时期
You two get along very well
你们两个相处得很好
Fully comply with organizational requirements
完全按照组织要求
Pack everything up here as soon as possible
尽快把所有东西打包到这里
Let’s go to Tianhai
我们去天海吧
It's time to adapt
是时候适应了
your new identity
你的新身份
Things that shouldn't be missed
不应该被遗漏的事情
as soon as possible
尽快地
I lived a happy life during this time
这段时间我过着幸福的生活
be my happy wife
做我幸福的妻子
my partner is still happy
我的伴侣仍然很高兴
all is well
一切都很好
but this is temporary
但这是暂时的
Maybe marriage will come back one day
也许婚姻有一天会回归
But that person
但那个人
Not necessarily you
不一定是你
Then it gets weird
然后就变得奇怪了
as a neighbor
作为邻居
Are you weird?
你很奇怪吗？
Looks good
看起来不错
keep the ring
保留戒指
It's better to sell it for money
最好还是卖掉换钱
worthless
一文不值
accept
收下
say
说话
The main card you get
您获得的主卡
Forged
伪造的
are you sure
你确定吗
The Office of National Security may step in
国家安全办公室可能会介入
What time will we arrive?
我们什么时候到达？
Understood
明白了
I'm on my way back
我正在回来的路上
Are you calling me?
你在打电话给我吗？
you are being watched
你被监视了
Looking for a way to escape
寻找逃脱的方法
OK
好的
what happened?
发生了什么？
there is nothing
没有什么
this is not a way out
这不是出路
Tianyang
天阳
The target has exited the highway early
目标已提前退出高速
no attention
没有关注
The way back to Tianhai
回天海的路
can he
他可以吗
Leo follows
狮子座紧随其后
they were discovered
他们被发现了
impossible
不可能的
Our process
我们的流程
always been hidden
一直都被隐藏着
Leo.
利奥.
Look at him. Follow him.
看着他。跟着他。
watch your movements
注意你的动作
we'll go right away
我们马上就去
you
你
what happened?
发生了什么？
there is nothing
没有什么
Why are you driving so fast?
你为什么开这么快？
target stop
目标停靠点
Location synced
位置已同步
in your car
在你的车里
I'll go there now
我现在就去那儿
Chu Yan
楚炎
I have some questions now
我现在有一些问题
Help me drive to Tianhai
帮我开车去天海
Can you drive a manual guardrail?
你会驾驶手动护栏吗？
I don't know how to drive
我不知道怎么开车
Why do you have a gun?
你为什么有枪？
Who are you?
你是谁？
What’s wrong with you?
你怎么了？
silent
沉默的
I can't now
我现在不能
I have to explain a lot to you
我必须向你解释很多
Let's break up here
我们在这里分手吧
What does separation mean?
分离是什么意思？
I don't like girls who talk a lot
我不喜欢爱说话的女孩
i know your parents
我认识你的父母
He lives at No. 23 Nanyuan
他家住南苑23号
I don't want to treat you like this
我不想这样对待你
go
去
Quickly
迅速地
let's go
我们走吧
sorry
对不起
he left again
他又离开了
Tianjin target has restored expressway
天津目标已恢复高速
I'm going to the parking lot
我要去停车场
come and see the situation
来看看情况
proceed as originally planned
按照原计划进行
to the payment terminal to help prevent this
到支付终端以帮助防止这种情况
OK
好的
you
你
The target is approaching
目标正在逼近
Be prepared to be stopped
做好被拦住的准备
Get ready to park quickly
赶紧准备停车
stop
停止
Where is Xiao Yi?
肖毅在哪里？
Call an ambulance quickly
赶紧叫救护车
And going up the mountain
还有上山
can't escape
无法逃脱
if you were me
如果你是我
I will choose the nearby mountain road
我会选择附近的山路
we are missing
我们失踪了
Escape implementation tools
逃生实施工具
Search along the mountain road
沿着山路寻找
OK
好的
look at her 2
看看她2
[About half an hour later]
【大约半小时后】
Is there a missing car from the police station?
警察局有车失踪吗？
Or a stolen car
或者偷来的车
I found it
我找到了
Someone pulled a motorcycle
有人拉了一辆摩托车
The victim called the police
受害人报了警
The license plate number is ZC02J
车牌号为ZC02J
There's not much gas in the car
车里的油不多了
The car owner is cheering and ready to go
车主欢呼雀跃准备出发
Can't escape
逃不掉
Follow that car immediately
立即跟随那辆车
There are also gas stations nearby
还有附近的加油站
Verified
已验证
There is a gas station 300 meters away
附近300米有加油站
direct
直接的
92 plus 20
92 加 20
i just left
我刚刚离开
Look at the surveillance cameras
看看监控摄像头
This black car is carrying him
这辆黑车载着他
There aren't many security cameras here
这里没有很多安全摄像头
It's impossible to catch up with him
追上他是不可能的
Did I annoy you?
我惹恼你了吗？
No
不
Tianhai is not safe
天海并不安全
I can't go back
我无法回去
I wore a ring
我戴了戒指
May he bless us beyond this stage
愿他保佑我们超越这个阶段
Next
下一个
The bosses asked me to give you a ride
老板们让我载你一程
when
什么时候
as soon as possible
尽快地
you have to go
你得走了
This mission is a huge loss
这次任务是一个巨大的损失
Someone has to be responsible
必须有人负责
that's why i
这就是为什么我
sorry
对不起
I think you are
我想你是
Goodbye me
再见我
We can only live as one person
我们只能作为一个人生活
I don't want to die in your hands
我不想死在你手里
After getting off the car
下车后
We will no longer be partners
我们将不再是合作伙伴
I'm waiting
我在等待
retain memory
保留记忆
maybe in the future
也许在将来
we will never meet again
我们永远不会再见面
Wow that
哇那个
if
如果
Are you OK?
你好吗？
Did you find the evidence?
你找到证据了吗？
a bit strange
有点奇怪
The place was cleaned up
这个地方被干净地处理掉了
no useful evidence
没有有用的证据
Even the trash can
就连垃圾桶
Clean
干净的
But two days later
但两天后
We will search carefully
我们会仔细寻找
I will notify you as soon as there is news
有消息我会第一时间通知你
where is the computer
电脑在哪里
Have you checked?
你检查了吗？
Computer Hard Drive Fan Page
电脑硬盘粉丝页面
zero is written
零被写入
All records
所有记录
has been completely deleted
已经被彻底删除了
Unable to recover
无法恢复
so i was thinking
所以我在想
Xiao Yi has already noticed
萧毅已经注意到了
He was prepared to retreat in advance
他提前做好了撤退的准备
If he has a sense of danger
如果他有危险意识
When he brought Chu Yan back to the city
当他带着楚炎回城的时候
This must be the case
一定是这样
Who helped him escape?
谁帮他逃走的
He's here to clean up the crime scene
他是来清理犯罪现场的
it's out of the question
这是不可能的
This has always been Xiao Yi's residence
这里一直是萧毅的住所
look at us
看着我们
And during this period
而在这个时期
nobody
没有人
he entered their house
他进入他们的房子
unless
除非
another door
另一扇门
Do you have?
有没有？
impossible
不可能的
accomplish
实现
go check it out
去检查一下
Who lives in this house?
谁住在这所房子里？
OK
好的
This person is about 170cm tall
此人身高170cm左右
medium build
中等身材
Shoes 37
鞋37
This is the photo from the camera
这是相机里的照片
in the bar
在酒吧里
Her height is very similar
她的身高很相似
Who lives here?
谁住在这里？
It should be Mr. Zhang
应该是张先生吧
Pretend to be a neighbor
假装是邻居
In fact he is a partner
事实上他是合伙人
Wow that
哇那个
did you find it?
你找到了吗？
I asked the nearby security guard
我问了附近的保安
Only someone who lives here can confirm
只有住在这里的人才能确认
She is a woman in her thirties
她是一个三十多岁的女人
Her name is Zhang Ruyun
她的名字叫张茹芸
Is he the master?
他是主人吗？
No
不
The original owner is a foreigner
原主人是外国人
Can't contact him now
现在联系不上他
Have you checked any nearby security cameras?
你检查过附近的监控摄像头吗？
Is there any live video?
有现场视频吗？
security system
保安系统
he was cheated
他被骗了
Monitor information within a week
一周内监测信息
deleted
已删除
what happened
发生了什么
He said
他说
maybe it's a woman
也许这是一个女人
Are you OK?
你好吗？
I am fine
我很好
I'll get you another bag
我再给你拿一个包
Thanks
谢谢
No need, no need
不需要，不需要
take it
拿去
thank you for your welcome
谢谢您的欢迎
Thanks
谢谢
Mr. Zhang
张先生
very cautious
非常谨慎
He is a difficult opponent
他是一个很难对付的对手
thank you all
谢谢你们
There is also an examination group
还有考试组
Check out these two rooms
检查这两个房间
Check it carefully
仔细检查一下
There must be an air leak
一定有漏气
Other effects
其他效果
we will do our best
我们会全力以赴
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
it's time
是时候了
Huang Ziqing
黄子清
He has contact with Gao Tianyang.
他和高天阳有联系。
He found
他发现
fellow spy
间谍同胞
He told Gao Tianyang
他告诉高天阳
That's it
就是这样
like i said
就像我说的
I'm still not sure
我还是不确定
He works for the national security
他为国安工作
Or does he want to plead guilty?
还是他想认罪？
Who are you
你是
She deliberately hid it from him
她故意向他隐瞒
he took advantage of me
他利用了我
Why should I avoid him?
我为什么要躲着他？
This is good
这很好
Today we will ask him face to face
今天我们当面问问他
Who works?
谁工作？
Why do we meet here?
为什么我们会在这里见面？
you want to travel
你想去旅行
OK
好的
let's go
我们走吧
where are we going?
我们去哪？
You'll know when we arrive
当我们到达时你就会知道
Thanks
谢谢
A lot of dishes
菜品很多
very beautiful
很漂亮
People who grew up by the sea
在海边长大的人
He's not bored yet
他还没无聊
scene itself
场景本身
But people are different
但人与人不同
Of course his mood is different
当然他的心情不一样
Lots of sweet words
很多甜言蜜语
i will believe
我会相信
since the first time
自从第一次
I met you at the bar
我在酒吧遇见了你
I know
我知道
i will definitely love you
我一定会爱你
But love at first sight is not reliable
但一见钟情并不可靠
Aren't you honest enough?
你还不够诚实吗？
Huang Ziqing grew up
黄子晴从小
Do you like lying?
你喜欢撒谎吗？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Cover up the night fog with false information
用虚假信息掩盖夜雾
Looks familiar
看上去很眼熟
when you lie
当你撒谎时
don't close your eyes
不要闭上眼睛
really cool
真的很酷
do not you?
你不是吗？
I can live in the night fog
我可以生活在夜雾之中
In the night fog
夜雾中
thank you for your cooperation
谢谢你的合作
this is correct
这是对的
we come from the same road
我们来自同一条路
but different
但不一样
I gave you the basic card
我给了你基本卡
until one day
直到有一天
You want to destroy this alliance
你想破坏这个联盟
you can kill me anytime
你随时可以杀了我
I can't even fight
我什至无法战斗
Really?
真的吗？
Did you give it to me?
你给我了吗？
for me?
为我？
I really thought
我真的以为
See you sincerely
真诚相见
Who knew we were deceiving each other?
谁知道我们在互相欺骗？
say what you want to say
说你想说的话
between us
我们之间
No need to speak
无需说话
Why did you lie to me?
你为什么骗我？
anything?
任何事物？
"Gao Tianyang" means "Gu'an"
“高天阳”就是“固安”
if you don't speak
如果你不说话
This means you agree to this
这意味着您同意这一点
Yes or no
是不是
No
不
I won't tell you
我不会告诉你
Because they have a system
因为他们有系统
unable to express
无法表达
your identity
您的身份
And you?
你呢？
What is your identity?
你的身份是什么？
Do you think
你认为
Are you going crazy?
你想疯了吗？
How should we deal with this problem?
我们该如何处理这个问题呢？
It's a pity you don't know
可惜你不知道
How much do I know?
我知道多少？
I'm not Guo An
我不是郭安
if i don't reach the truth
如果我没有达到真理
I won't come to see you
我不会来见你
I hope so
但愿如此
explanation to me
给我的解释
Who gave you permission to investigate me?
谁允许你调查我的？
Does it matter?
这重要吗？
Yes
是的
I should know where you stand
我应该知道你的立场
Who are you
你是
Or are you a spy?
或者你是间谍？
to investigate me
为了调查我
as a friend
作为一个朋友
as an ally
作为盟友
For you
为你
if you really
如果你真的
Verify your true identity
验证您的真实身份
You don't need to be so sneaky
你不需要这样偷偷摸摸
but if you
但如果你
as a spy
作为间谍
I am disappointed
我很失望
Still trying to deal with the night fog
仍在努力应对夜雾
correct
正确的
Yewu asked me to go see you
夜雾叫我去看看你
but i am
但我是
I want to know the truth
我想知道真相
Huang Ziqing
黄子清
Did you lie to me?
你骗我了吗？
Are you lying to me?
你在对我说谎吗？
since we met
自从我们相遇
so we play games
所以我们玩游戏
until we go out
直到我们出去
all of these
所有这些
in your plan
在你的计划中
you always lie to me
你总是对我撒谎
You're always using me, aren't you?
你总是在利用我，不是吗？
I didn't take advantage of you
我没有利用你
i am saving you
我正在拯救你
you still lie to me
你还是对我撒谎
Even now you're lying to me
即使现在你也在对我撒谎
Huang Ziqing
黄子清
I just want to ask you
我只想问你
Is it your heart?
是你的心吗
Don't you feel guilty about me?
你对我不感到愧疚吗？
Yes or no?
是不是？
i thought i hurt you
我以为我伤害了你
I really thought
我真的以为
When I was in Macau
我在澳门的时候
I was in Macau
我当时在澳门
So I didn't think anything
所以我没想什么
I will come back to save you
我会回来救你
But now it seems
但现在看来
you are lying to me
你在骗我
at first
起初
this is me
这就是我
I am silly Huang Ziqing
我是傻黄子晴
You're the stupidest thing I've ever done
你是我做过的最愚蠢的事
Are you still helping Ye Wu?
你是否还在帮助夜雾
if you continue like this
如果你继续这样
no one can save you
没有人能拯救你
I don't want you to save me
我不想让你来救我
I can go out
我可以出去
I'm back for you
我为你回来了
Lorak
洛拉克
I am free
我是自由的
Huang Ziqing, do you know?
黄子晴你知道吗？
And you
你呢
at any time
随时
Let Gao Tianyang catch me.
让高天阳来抓我。
Yes or no?
是不是？
Yes or no
是不是
say
说话
Say something, answer me
说句话，回答我
sorry
对不起
Do you really think so?
你真的这么认为吗？
Say I don't know anything?
说我什么都不知道？
you are listening to me
你在听我说话
You act with me all the time
你时时刻刻跟我一起演戏
And your acting skills are very good
而且你演技很好
You almost lied to me
你差点就骗了我
but do you think
但你认为
that love
那份爱
you can perform
你可以表演
I hope
我希望
face me honestly
诚实地面对我
Give me an explanation
给我一个解释
OK
好的
After I came back from Macau
我从澳门回来后
my identity
我的身份
Discovered by his brother
被弟弟发现了
He cares about our feelings
他很关心我们的感受
He didn't tell about this
这件事他没有告诉
To national security
致国安
but he asked me
但他问我
Not working for spies
不为间谍工作
He asked me to provide him with evidence
他让我给他提供证据
To help solve the case
为帮助破案
make an achievement
取得成就
This is a fact
这是事实
Why are you avoiding me?
你为什么躲着我？
this matter
这件事
A third party cannot know
第三人无法知道
but I do not have
但我没有
i'm using you
我在利用你
i always want to
我一直想
Be your scapegoat
成为你的替罪羊
take you to the beach
带你去海滩
Night fog helps
夜雾有帮助
no future
没有未来
What's wrong with you?
你有什么错？
What have you achieved?
你取得了哪些成就？
you are always at the beach
你总是在海滩
real dangerous man
真正的危险人物
this is me
这就是我
if you are in danger
如果你有危险
he won't leave you
他不会离开你
Ignore you
不理你
but we are all different
但我们都是不同的
They are taking advantage of my family's safety.
他们正在利用我家人的安全
come threaten me
来威胁我
i must promise
我必须保证
their safety
他们的安全
so
所以
I have no chance to go ashore
我已经没有机会上岸了
So I'm the only one who can save you
所以我是唯一能拯救你的人
I'm here to tell you today
今天我来告诉你
I found a spy
我发现了一个间谍
He is also a gamer
他也是一名游戏玩家
Discover that special game
发现那个特别的游戏
When he found out everything was a scam
当他发现一切都是骗局之后
Might ruin the dream
可能会毁了梦想
virtual life is over
虚拟生活结束了
reality must be punished
现实必须受到惩罚
So that's it now
所以现在就是这样
He went to surrender
他去投降了
for him
为了他
This is the best result
这是最好的结果
Ways I can save myself
我可以拯救自己的方法
He was an informant for Gao Tianyang
是给高天阳做线人
you are my partner
你是我的伙伴
always
总是
I won't give it to you
我不给你
you must tell me
你必须告诉我
tell me these things
告诉我这些事情
Sadness is shown really well.
悲伤的表现真的很好
I'm touched by both of you
我被你们俩感动了
we will meet again
我们会再见面的
You set a trap for me
你为我设下陷阱
sorry
对不起
For a betrayal like yours
对于像你这样的背叛
Don't use any more tricks
不要再使用任何技巧
how can we
我们怎样才能
to know the truth
要知道真相
i can't do anything
我什么也做不了
you are fighting
你在战斗
you have to take me here
你必须带我来这里
I can't offend you
我不能冒犯你
I can't offend Gao Tianyang.
我不能得罪高天阳。
I have no idea
我不知道
Will he come to your rescue?
他会来救你吗？
you
你
If you dare to look for it
如果你敢去寻找
i think you are brave
我认为你很勇敢
But I guess you don't dare
但我猜你不敢
you are just a bully
你只是一个恶霸
we are gamers
我们是游戏玩家
don't motivate me
别激励我
I won't embarrass you
我不会让你难堪
Don't embarrass me, okay?
别让我难堪好吗？
I gotta go
我要走了
Didn't you say that?
你没说吗？
don't embarrass me
别让我难堪
As long as you cooperate with us
只要您与我们合作
I will treat you well
我会好好待你的
How can I work with you?
我如何与你合作？
What did you say to the NSA?
你对国家安全局说了什么？
national security office
国家安全办公室
I don't know who the National Security Agency is
我不知道国安局是谁
I am Gao Tianyang's informant.
我是高天阳的线人。
he is my brother
他是我兄弟
Do you know how to help me?
你知道如何帮助我吗？
how can i help you
我该如何帮助你
I told him
我告诉他了
The task you gave me
你给我的任务
Your last fetched data
您上次获取的数据
He is the one who asked you to revise
他是要求你修改的人
Yes
是的
you are honest
你很诚实
I feel uncomfortable
我觉得不舒服
What should I tell you?
我该怎么告诉你呢？
He forced me to say
他强迫我说
but you don't believe me
但你不相信我
Are you cheap?
你便宜吗？
you deceived us
你欺骗了我们
you are very frank
你很坦诚
what can I do?
我能做些什么？
you must be punished
你必须受到惩罚
What punishment?
什么惩罚？
hope you can figure it out
希望你能弄清楚情况
It's impossible to come back alive
活着回来是不可能的